Ethan Holen

COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY CLASS OF 2022, B.S. COMPUTER SCIENCE

□720-326-5046 | Sethanholen@gmail.com | Sethanholen.com | Dethanholen |

Summarv 5 4 1

Current IOS Developer, and undergraduate at Colorado State University with experience in both the software and hardware side of the tech industry as well as the medical field. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys backpacking, mountain biking and camping in the wilds of Colorado. Interested in gaining new and interesting experiences in the field of Computer Science.

Education .

COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY(COLLEGE OF NATURAL SCIENCES)

Fort Collins, CO

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

• Relevant Coursework: Intro to Java Programming (Java)

SAINT LOUIS UNIVERSITY(COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES)

Saint Louis, MO

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, PRE MED

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

• Relevant Coursework: Managing Big Data (Python)

Valor Christian High School

Highlands Ranch, CO Aug. 2014 - May. 2018

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

• Relevant Coursework: AP Computer Science (Java)

Work Experience

 IOS Development
 Denver CO

 IOS Developer
 May. 2019 - Present

• Wrote custom IOS Application for Douglas County Sheriffs Office

• Designed and Created a secure back-end using AWS Lambda and API Gateway

Valor Christian High School

Highlands Ranch, CO.

Aug. 2016 - May. 2018

IT INTERN

• Provided hardware and software solutions for help desk tickets

- Helped manage a JAMF environment of 550 Apple devices
- Setup and management of 20 Aerohive network access points
- Setup and management of 20 Aeronive network access points

Express Care Cheyenne, WY

• Assisted Doctor or PA on call as a scribe

- Vitals and initial patient charts
- Strep, urine and vision tests

Extracurricular Activity _

May. 2016 - Jul. 2016

Extra dan mada

Skills & Talents

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

PERSONAL

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

- · Programming Languages: Java, Python, HTML, CSS, Bash, Swift
- Software: OSX, Windows, Linux, AWS, Xcode, Personal Website
- Hardware: Custom PC, Mac Repairs, Raspberry Pi

Eagle Scout - Troop 102 Greenwood Village, CO

PATROL LEADER, TROOP HISTORIAN

Sep. 2011 - May. 2015

- · Learned Leadership and organization through positions of patrol leader and troop historian
- Project: Build garden and fence around local monastery

Medical Missions Work Ethiopia

• Assisted physicians with scribe work and basic medical tests.

Aug. 2017

Video: https://govalor.com/discovery-ethiopia-video/